A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Tunis, Tunisia Field Office Files FA645
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Population, 1962-1976; VII
  - Population -- General -- Evaluation Mission Review 1972 for North Africa, Part I, Sep 1971-Apr 1972 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Evaluation Mission Review 1972 for North Africa, Part II (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- French Family Planning, Part I, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- French Family Planning, Part II, Dec 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Information, 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Information IV, Jun 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- ICOMP -- Wickham, R.S., 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Dr. Jongmans Report and Correspondence, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Population Office Mailings, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Population Office Questionnaire on Management of Family Programs, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General, Special Topics -- Population Strategy Review, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Beyond Family Planning -- Reports, 1969-1975 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Beyond Family Planning, Oct 1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Reports Re: Ford Foundation Supported Population Studies Centers, Bellagio Conference, Women's Roles, etc., 1973 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Bellagio Population Group -- Project Proposals, International Division Conference Memo, Reports, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Elisabeth Mueller (Population Council) -- Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Ford and Rockefeller Foundations -- Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, Part I, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Ford and Rockefeller Foundations Program in Support of Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, Part II, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Project Proposal -- Taylor/Berelson Scheme Re: Family Planning, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Program Proposal -- Population Association of Africa, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Proposal for a Ford Foundation Mission to Survey Project Possibilities in Demographic and Social Science Research in Population in West Africa, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Population -- "Rolling Mission" (Family Planning Review Mission, January 22-26, 1973) -- Maghreb, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - "Health and Nutrition in India: Recommendations for Ford Foundation Support" by Davidson R. Gwatkin, Jan 1974 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Fertility, and Abortion in Africa and Developing Countries -- Reports, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population -- Africa (and elsewhere) -- Reports, Travel Logs, Ford Foundation Reprint, Conference Memoranda and Agenda, 1964-1970 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population -- Reports, 1965-1974 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population, Social Science Research on Population and Development -- Memoranda and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (1/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (2/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (3/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (4/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (5/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (6/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (7/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences, Seminars and Workshops -- General, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences, Seminars and Workshops -- General, Jun 1974-1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- African Population Conferences, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Micro-Economics Seminar Re: Fertility (Tunis, February 1972), Feb 1972 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Population Meeting (Elsinore, Denmark, June 1972), Jun 1972 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Third Population Conference (Bellagio, Italy) -- Summary and Projections -- Moderator, David Bell, May 12, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Tentative Plans for Workshop jointly Sponsored by Inst. Nat. du P.F. et de la P.M.I. Ministry of Health, Tunisia, and Community and Family Study Center, University of Chicago (Tunis, July/Aug 1973), 1972 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- International Union for the Scientific Study of Population -- Liege Conference, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- International Conference on the Physician and Population Change (Stockholm, September 4-6, 1974), Sep 4-6, 1974 (Box 21)
- Public Administration, 1964-1968; VIII
  - "Etude Preliminaire sur la Reform Administrative en Algerie", Jan 1966 (Box 21)
  - "Ford Foundation Public Administration Program in Tunisia" -- A Report to David Heaps from Maxwell Lehman, Oct 1968 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Algeria -- Administrative Reform, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Algeria -- Civil Service, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Pan-Maghrebian Meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Tunisia -- National School of Administration -- Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
- Appendix A: Reports, 1966-1973
  - Gwatkin, Davidson R.; Annual Program Report -- Population and Family Planning in West Africa, Dec 1969 (Report #019938)
  - Kelly, George H.; Activities Report, Dec 12, 1966 (Report #019935)
  - Marcoux, Alain; The Ford Foundation, Population Council North African Population Program in Retrospect, Dec 1975 (Report #019937)
  - Nagel, John; What is the Population, Family Planning Field doing about Utilizing Research, Nov 16, 1973 (Report #019939)
  - Urquidu, John and Maxwell Lehman; Ecole Nationale D'Administration -- The Library, Jan 1968 (Report #019936)